offer-dynamics.com 2018-10-05

# Privacy Policy - OfferDynamics

**1\. INCLUSION OF PERSONAL DATA IN THE FILES OF AEDGE PERFORMANCE FILES:**

Pursuant to the provisions of Organic Law 15/1999 of 13 December pertaining to Personal Data Protection, all such information the User provides through the website (hereinafter, the “Website”) shall be collected and processed in files owned by AEDGE PERFORMANCE BCN, S.L.U (hereinafter referred to as “AEDGE PERFORMANCE” or “the Company”) for the purposes of providing the services requested by the User, replying to their requests and keeping the User informed of the products and services marketed by the AEDGE PERFORMANCE, including by way of electronic means. 

If you do not wish to receive this type of electronic correspondence (e-mails), you may do so by sending an e-mail to [legal@offer-dynamics.com](mailto:legal@offer-dynamics.com). 

The completion of all information marked as mandatory on this Website is necessary in order to ensure optimum provision of the services offered to the User. If this data is not provided, the AEDGE PERFORMANCE does not guarantee that the information and services requested may be offered, correctly supplied or meet the needs of the User. 

The AEDGE PERFORMANCE informs that it has implemented security measures of a technical and organizational measure to ensure the security of the User’s personal data and avoid its alteration, loss, and / or unauthorized access, given the state of technology the nature of the data stored and the risks they are exposed, whether from human action or the physical or natural environment. The foregoing is pursuant to the provisions of Article 9 of the Spanish Organic Law on Personal Data Protection. 

**2\. PURPOSE OF DATA COLLECTION:**

With each interaction between your device and our ad servers we collect certain information, which we will describe below. We use this information in order to help deliver more interesting and relevant ads to you, in order to provide to our customers and partners reports that contain aggregated data (for instance, the number of ads delivered each day, the number of clicks on those ads, and so on), in order to analyze trends, and in order to perform fraud detection. 

**3\. INFORMATION COLLECTED:**

We do not collect personally identifiable information about you. We do, however, record and use information that is not personally identifiable, including but not limited to the following:  
\- the IP address of your device on the internet, to do geo-targeting, to identify your mobile operator, connection type, and other details;  
\- the ‘user agent’ of your browser or application, and other relevant request headers, to help us identify your device type;  
\- the date and time of the ad request or interaction;  
\- and a unique identifier, such as an HTTP cookie or your device advertising identifier, that enables us not to show you the same ad over and over again.  
We also encourage (but do not require) our publishers to share with us additional information that is not personally identifiable information, but that we may use in order to improve ad relevance. This data may include:  
\- your age or age range, if known to the publisher;  
\- your gender, if known to the publisher;  
\- your user geographic location, if known to the publisher. 

**4\. USE OF INFORMATION:**

We may use this non personally identifiable information along with our technology in order to provide ads that are likely to be more interesting and more relevant to users to target advertising (this is also known as behavioral, or interest-based advertising).  
We sometimes use cookies or device identifiers to help us track whether you complete specific actions on an advertiser’s web site or application, as this is needed for analytical purposes, and in order to monitor the performance of our ads. These cookies or identifiers use the domain name "contextual-serving.com" and expire within 30 days.  
We may also use some of this data to provide interest-based advertising. As a general rule, we don’t collect personally identifiable information. 

**5\. OPT-OUT:**

Opting Out is easy; when a you opt-out we will no longer be able to recognize and serve contextual or retargeted advertising to you. By you clicking on the opt-out button below, we will recognize that you are no longer are interested in receiving our advertising and will disable Aedgency's and its Partners the ability to deliver ads to you. 

**6\. SUBMISSION OF DATA FOR STAFF SELECTION:**

Curriculum vitaes submitted by the User to the Company will be used for the sole purpose of responding to applications for employment related to jobs advertised. By providing your personal information, you acknowledge that the data provided is yours and is accurate and true. 

**7\. PROHIBITION ON REGISTRATION BY MINORS:**

Persons under the age of 14 must obtain prior consent from their parents or guardians before providing their personal information to the Company. If you are a minor, please ask your parents or guardians to contact us first. 

**8\. EXERCISE OF RIGHTS:**

The User may exercise their rights to access, rectification, cancellation and opposition by sending an e-mail to legal@offer-dynamics.com or by writing to AEDGE PERFORMANCE, Avenida Diagonal 579, Planta 7ª, 08014, Barcelona. In either case, the User must send a copy of his/her identity card, passport or other valid form of identification. 

**9\. COMMUNICATION OF INFORMATION BY THE USER:**

Before providing personal information belonging to third parties through the Website, the User must obtain their prior express consent and inform the parties concerned of the terms of this Privacy Policy. The User undertakes to not hold the Company liable for any possible claim, fine or penalty it may be obliged to bear as a result of the User’s breach of the obligations set forth in this clause. 

**10\. COOKIES**

The Company may use cookies either directly or through third parties contracted for the provision of measurement services when the User accesses the Website. Cookies are files sent to the browser from a web server to record the User’s activities on the website. The cookies used by the Website are only associated with one anonymous user and their computer, and consequently, the User's personal data is not provided by the cookies. Through the use of cookies, the server hosting the Website may recognise the browser used by the User in order to make web browsing simpler, for example by granting access for users who have previously registered to areas, services, promotions or competitions reserved exclusively for users without having to register every time they visit the Web site. Cookies are also used to measure web site audience and traffic parameters and to monitor the progress and number of visits. Please refer to your web browser’s instructions and manuals for further information. To use the Website, the User does not have to allow the installation of cookies sent by the Web site or third parties acting on behalf of the Company; however, the User may have to log in each time for those services requiring previous registration or “login”. 

**11\. COOKIES AND THIRD PARTY COOKIES**

By using the Website, the User acknowledges and accepts that the following types of cookies are used: 

Session Cookies: These types of cookies allow the Company to retrieve and store data while the User accesses a website.  
Persistent Cookies: These types of cookies are stored in the User’s device and can be accessed and processed during a period of time determined by the Company.  
Advertising Cookies: These types of cookies are used by the Company which allow managing the personalization of the offers and advertising when the User is visiting a webpage or searching online. To do so, the User’s Internet browsing habits can be analyzed in order to display ads related to his/her browsing profile.  
The User can allow, block or deleted the installed cookies on his/her device through the browser settings of his/her browser:   
For Internet Explorer, click [here](http://windows.microsoft.com/is-is/internet-explorer/delete-manage-cookies#ie=ie-10)  
For Mozilla Firefox, click [here](https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/cookies-information-websites-store-on-your-computer)  
For Google Chrome, click [here](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en)  
For Safari, click [here](http://support.apple.com/kb/HT1677?viewlocale=en_US)  
For Opera, click [here](http://www.opera.com/help/tutorials/security/privacy/)  
The User can also review more information regarding the use of cookies at <http://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/your-ad-choices> and <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>
